<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Tighe's Daily Feed</title>
    <link>https://tighebrary.io</link>
    <description>This is a test feed. I'm trying to create daily episodes.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://tighebrary.io/images/alex-tighe-podcast-artwork.png</url>
      <title>Alex Tighe's Daily Feed</title>
      <link>https://tighebrary.io</link>
    </image>
    <ns0:category text="Society &amp; Culture"> <ns0:category text="Personal Journals" /></ns0:category>
    <ns0:explicit>false</ns0:explicit>
    <ns0:author>Alex Tighe</ns0:author>
    <ns0:image href="https://tighebrary.io/images/alex-tighe-podcast-artwork.png" />

    <item>
      <title>Rising from the Ashes: The Journey of Hope</title><description>In this inspiring episode, we share the remarkable story of Mia, a young woman whose life took an unexpected turn due to a devastating fire. Through resilience and the power of community, Mia transforms her tragedy into a source of hope and motivation for others. Join us as we explore the beauty of human strength and the light that can emerge from even the darkest places.</description><pubDate>2024-11-25T15:37:09.506805</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3" length="3670848" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3</guid>
    </item>
  
    <item>
      <title>NYC in Flux: Navigating the Impact of Rising Rents</title><description>In today's episode, we delve into the pressing issue of rising rent prices in New York City. As gentrification continues to shape neighborhoods, many residents find themselves struggling to keep up with skyrocketing costs. We explore the factors contributing to this crisis, hear from affected tenants, and discuss potential solutions with housing advocates and experts.</description><pubDate>2024-11-25T17:48:16.037060</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3" length="3670848" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    
  <item>
    <title>**Marvels of Manhattan: New York City Unveils New Transit Plans**</title><description>**In today's episode, we dive into the latest news from New York City as the city unveils an ambitious plan to enhance its public transit system. We explore what this means for commuters and the future of urban mobility.**</description><pubDate>2024-11-25T17:55:54.937480</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3" length="3670848" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>"City Reflections: New York's Climate Resilience Initiatives"</title><description>In today's episode, we dive into New York City's latest initiatives aimed at combating climate change and enhancing urban resilience. Learn about the city's strategic plans and innovative projects designed to protect vulnerable communities from extreme weather events.</description><pubDate>2024-11-25T18:44:14.530496</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3" length="3670848" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/7am-star-casino-rick-music-clip.mp3</guid>
  </item>
  <item><title>NYC’s Struggle with Rising Rent: A Crisis for Communities</title><description>In this episode, we explore the latest news surrounding New York City's escalating rent crisis, examining how its impact is reverberating through communities, businesses, and families. We delve into the causes behind the surge and discuss potential solutions being proposed by local leaders.</description><pubDate>2024-12-05T18:46:02.533311+00:00</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-05T18:46:02.531834+00:00.mp3" length="798720" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-05T18:46:02.531834+00:00.mp3</guid></item></channel>
</rss>