<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex Tighe's Daily Feed</title>
    <link>https://tighebrary.io</link>
    <description>This is a test feed. I'm trying to create daily episodes.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://tighebrary.io/images/alex-tighe-podcast-artwork.png</url>
      <title>Alex Tighe's Daily Feed</title>
      <link>https://tighebrary.io</link>
    </image>
    <ns0:category text="Society &amp; Culture">
      <ns0:category text="Personal Journals" />
    </ns0:category>
    <ns0:explicit>false</ns0:explicit>
    <ns0:author>Alex Tighe</ns0:author>
    <ns0:image href="https://tighebrary.io/images/alex-tighe-podcast-artwork.png" />

    <item>
      <title>NYC’s Struggle with Rising Rent: A Crisis for Communities</title>
      <description>In this episode, we explore the latest news surrounding New York City's escalating rent crisis, examining how its impact is reverberating through communities, businesses, and families. We delve into the causes behind the surge and discuss potential solutions being proposed by local leaders.</description>
      <pubDate>2024-12-05T18:46:02.533311+00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-05T18:46:02.531834+00:00.mp3" length="798720" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-05T18:46:02.531834+00:00.mp3</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Unpacking New York City's Historic Climate Action Plan</title>
      <description>In today's episode, we delve into New York City's ambitious new climate action plan, which aims to significantly reduce carbon emissions and combat climate change with innovative strategies and sustainability initiatives.</description>
      <pubDate>2024-12-07T09:35:20.803960+00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-07T09:35:20.802924+00:00.mp3" length="752160" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-07T09:35:20.802924+00:00.mp3</guid>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>New York City Faces Housing Crisis: A Call for Solutions</title>
      <description>In today's episode, we delve into the latest developments surrounding New York City's escalating housing crisis. With skyrocketing rents and a limited number of affordable housing units, residents are feeling the squeeze. We discuss city officials' proposed measures to combat the crisis, including increased funding for affordable housing projects and zoning reforms. We also explore the implications of these challenges on the diverse communities within the city and the potential long-term solutions that could bring relief to New Yorkers. Tune in for a deep dive into this critical issue facing the Big Apple.</description>
      <pubDate>2024-12-07T10:42:11.293355+00:00</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-07T10:42:11.292272+00:00.mp3" length="836640" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-07T10:42:11.292272+00:00.mp3</guid>
    </item>
  <item><title>"Unprecedented Flooding Strikes New York City"</title><description>In today's episode, we delve into the devastating flooding that has hit New York City, causing chaos across boroughs and affecting thousands. </description><pubDate>2024-12-08T17:21:01.385520+00:00</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-08T17:21:01.382784+00:00.mp3" length="728640" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-08T17:21:01.382784+00:00.mp3</guid></item><item><title>New York City Embraces Sustainability with Latest Green Initiatives</title><description>In today's episode, we dive into New York City's groundbreaking efforts to enhance sustainability and combat climate change, highlighting new initiatives that aim to redefine urban living.</description><pubDate>2024-12-09T09:39:38.743693+00:00</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-09T09:39:38.742706+00:00.mp3" length="757920" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-09T09:39:38.742706+00:00.mp3</guid></item><item><title>"NYC's Bold Move: Striking Down the Eviction Crisis"</title><description>In today's episode, we delve into New York City's groundbreaking decision to tackle the eviction crisis head-on. With historic legislation passed, thousands of vulnerable tenants now have renewed protections against displacement.</description><pubDate>2024-12-10T09:39:36.781510+00:00</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-10T09:39:36.780735+00:00.mp3" length="811200" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-10T09:39:36.780735+00:00.mp3</guid></item><item><title>New York City's Climate Initiative: A Bold Step Forward</title><description>This episode explores New York City's latest groundbreaking climate initiative aimed at significantly reducing emissions and enhancing sustainability. </description><pubDate>2024-12-11T09:38:42.155266+00:00</pubDate><enclosure url="https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-11T09:38:42.154431+00:00.mp3" length="801120" type="audio/mpeg" /><guid>https://tighebrary.io/audio/gpt/2024-12-11T09:38:42.154431+00:00.mp3</guid></item></channel>
</rss>